저녁 초대해줘서 고마워
Thank you guys for having us over.
Oh! Yeah, this is fun, couples night
재미있는 커플들만의 밤이야
Yeah, I don't know why we hang out
with married couples more often
난 왜 우리가 결혼한 커플들과
함께 자주 안노는지 모르겠어
Well, because every time we do, you make jokes about swinging and scare them away.
그건 우리가 커플들과 만날 때마다
네가 스와핑에 관한 농담을 해서
그것 때문에 다른 커플들이
놀라서 도망가서 그런 거잖아
너 그 포루투갈 커플 말하는 거야?
You mean that Portuguese couple?
Yeah, like you wouldn't have done it
너도 하고 싶었으면서...
안녕, 얘들아~
굉장한 소식이 있어
Hey, you guys... I have great news
로스, 우리 지금
저녁 먹고 있는 중이었는데...
Ross, we're kind of in the middle of diner here
그래? 난 벌써 먹었는데...
또 먹지 뭐
Oh, well, er, I already ate, but sure...!
오늘 무슨 일이 있었는지 맞춰봐
Guess what happened at work today...
공룡이 백만년 전에 죽었냐?
A dinosaur died a million years ago?
6,500만년 전에 죽었고
Try sixty-five million years ago, and then try sssshhhhhh....
조용히 좀 해봐
내 종신 재직권에 대한
평가가 있었는데
My tenure review board met today
and I hear it's looking really good.
정말 가능성이 있어 보인다는
이야기를 들었어
Wow!
너희들 이런 걸 학계에서
뭐라고 하는 지나 알아?
Yeah. Do you have any idea what this means in academic circles, uh?
I am gonna get laid
내가 섹스를 하게 될 거란 얘기야!
안녕, 얘들아~
Hi you guys
Ooh, Italian!
이태리 음식이다!
No one wanted seconds, right?
두번째 식사는 아무도
좋아하지 않아, 맞지?
No, no. I-I'm good
아니, 난 좋은데
너희들은 상상도 못했을 거야
Hey you guys... You're never gonna believe it.
This headhunter called me
헤드헌터가 전화를 했는데
내일 구찌 면접이 있어
I have a meeting tomorrow with Gucci. Gucci wants me.
구찌가 나를 원해
나는 종신 재임 교수야
I'm up for tenure
축하해~
Congratulations!
너도 축하해~ 이게 웬 일이야
You too! What are the odds?
Ooh!
무슨 일 있게?
Guess what?
드디어 이빨에 껴있던 씨를 빼냈어
I finally got that seed out of my teeth
누가 그런 것에 기뻐하겠어?
I don't know who I'm happiest for...
내가 기뻐하지!
I do, he's been working on that all day!
조이가 그거 빼려고
하루종일 애썼단 말이야
FㆍRㆍIㆍEㆍNㆍDㆍS
10x14 The one with Princess Consuela
10x14 The One With Princess Consuela
[제작]민경주 marinmin0266@hotmail.com
[제 작]
코리아닷컴 프렌즈동호회 자막팀
안미연님이 올리신 대본으로 만들었습니다.
즐겁게 감상하시길....
[해 석]
홍현희(tatler@korea.com)
수정사항은 marinmin0266@hotmail.com으로...
[테스터]
박혜연(hyrp002@korea.com)
[싱 커]
김은진(yeooo4@korea.com)
임의 수정 및 상업적용도의 사용을 금합니다
수정사항은 피드백 게시판에 남겨주세요
(club.korea.com/friends)
모니카, 너 겔러에서 빙으로
이름 바꾸는 거 이상하지 않았어?
Hey Mon? Was it weird changing your name to Geller-Bing?
아니
No, no. It felt nice to acknowledge this
그건 결혼한 걸 알리는 멋진 풍습이야
어디서 바꿨는데?
Where did you go to do it?
이름부, 국에서...?
Uhm the... the ministry... of names... bureau...
자기 안바꿨네?!
YOU NEVER DID IT!
I'm sorry. It's just the idea of being an official Bing.
미안해, 난 그냥 내 이름이
공식적인 빙이 된다는 게...
Hey! I will have you know that...
내가 알게 해줄게
아니야... 우리 아기 성을
겔러라고 부르자
Aah, who am I kidding. Let's call the kid Geller and let Bing die with me.
빙은 나랑 같이 죽게 내버려 둬
-Here you go.
-Thanks!
- 여기
- 고마워
자기야, 내가 자기 성을
따르는 게 좋겠어?
Honey, would you want me to take your name?
Oh, it's just... It's up to you. It's your name. You've got to live with it.
자기 마음대로 해
자기 이름이잖아
자기가 달고 사는 건데
All right, let's see, call me mrs Hannigan
봐봐, 날 헤니건 부인이라고 불러
헤니건 부인?
Mrs Hannigan?
내가 지금 뭔가에
집중하고 있는 게 안보여?
What? Can't you see I'm in the middle of something? Ooh, I like it
오! 좋은데?
안녕, 얘들아~
Hey guys
안녕, 조~ 우리 새 집에 몇가지 좀
체크할 게 있는데 같이 좀 가줄래?
Hey Joe! We've got a couple of things
we've got to check out at the new house.
You want to come with us?
아니, 됐어
No, thank you
우리 이사하는거 별로 안좋아하는 건
알지만 너만 안와봤어
I know you're not happy about us moving, but you're the only one who hasn't seen the house.
같이 가자
시내에서도 얼마나 가까운데
Yeah, come with us. You'll see how close it is to the city
But no, it's not close
하나도 안가까워
조건부 날인 증서라고 했어?
You said it was in escrow?
I couldn't even find it on the map
지도에도 안나와있더라
조이, 제발 가자~
우리에게는 의미 있는 일이야
Joey, please come. It would mean so much to us
그거 알아? 너희는 내 친구고
You know what? You are my friends,
I wanna be supportive, I will come with you. SHOTGUN!
난 지지해주고 싶고... 갈 거야
억지로
젠장
Damn it!
- 나중에 보자
- 그래
See you guys later
Okay!
11시에 데리러 올게
가준다니 정말 고마워
I'll pick you up at eleven. So glad you're coming
잘했어
우린 정말 네가 성숙해졌다고 봐
Good for you. That was really mature
아니야, 진짜 내가
그 거지같은 새 집에 가는 이유는
What? No, the only reason I'm going to their stupid new house
여러가지 나쁜 점들을
지적하러 가는 거야
is so I can point out everything that's wrong with it, so they don't move. I'm gonna make them stay here.
난 걔네들 이사 못가게 할 거야
이상하게 성숙했네...
You're a strange kind of grown-up
조이, 다른 사람들이 하고 싶어하지
않는 걸 억지로 하게 할 수는 없어
Joey, you can't make someone do something they don't want to do
내 말을 들어
Believe me, there's something I've been trying to get Mike to do in bed and there's... he's just...
내가 마이크한테 침대에서
뭘 좀 하게 하려했는데 마이크는...
잠깐만... 우리 지금 그거
얘기하는 게 아니잖아
Woo-wo-hey-hey-hey... Can we not talk about that right now?
알았어, 내숭쟁이
All right, prude...
Look, Monica and Chandler really love this house. You are not gonna talk them into staying here
모니카랑 챈들러는 그 집
정말 좋아해
넌 걔네보고 여기 강제로
있으라고 얘기하면 안되는 거야
Hey, hey... I can convince people to do anything, you know
난 사람들한테 뭐든지
설득시킬 수 있어
I bet I can even get Mike to do that "thing". What is it?
내가 마이크한테
아까 네가 말한 거 부탁해볼게
그게 뭔데?
난 그런 거 못도와줘!! 세상에...
I AM NOT GONNA HELP YOU DO THAT! Goodbye!
안녕하세요, 저 구찌의
켐블씨를 만나러 왔는데요
Hi, I'm here to see mr Campbell... with Gucci
예약이 아마 구찌로 되어 있을 거에요
The reservation is probably under Gucci
It's spelled like Gukki, which could be confusing.
스펠링이 거키로 읽혀서
헷갈릴 수도 있어요
캠블씨는 아직 안오셨는데요
Mr Campbell's not here yet. Let me show you to his table
예약 테이블로 안내해 드리겠습니다
오, 맙소사!!
Oh my God! That's my boss.You have to seat us somewhere else
저 사람 제 상사잖아요
다른 곳으로 안내해주세요
I'm sorry. That's always mr Campbell's table
죄송합니다, 어디까지나 이 테이블이
캠블씨의 예약석입니다
하지만 제 상사가 절 보면 안되는데요
But my... but my boss cannot see me.
I'm interviewing for another job
제가 지금 다른 직장 면접을
보는 것이거든요
알아요, 거키 면접이요
I know. With Gukki
레이첼?
Rachel?
네, 안녕하세요~ 저 데이트 해요
Hi... I'm on a date...
잘 됐네요!
That's great!
네~ 정말 힘들어요
Yeah, it is. Yeah, you know, it's tough. Single mom, career... You gotta get out there
미혼모에서, 직장여성에서
탈출해야 하거든요!
네, 힘내야 되겠네요
Well, you got uhm... good energy
레이첼?
-Rachel?
-Yes,hi!
네, 안녕하세요!
제임스 캠블이라고 합니다
James Campbell...
Hi!Excuse us
실례할게요
- 앉으시죠
- 네
Oh, yeah... Oh he's cute!
멋있죠?
So... your resume is quite impressive.
이력서가 상당히 인상적이더군요
Wha... My resume? I wouldn't... I wouldn't call my online dating profile a resume
아, 제 이력서요?
저는 제 온라인 미팅의 자기 소개서를
이력서라고 부르지는 않는데요
미팅 자기 소개서요?
Dating profile? I-I-I'm talking about the work resume
저는 이력서를 말하는 건데요?
La la la la ~~~~~
요즘은 그냥 이유없이 노래부르는
사람들이 없어졌네요 그죠?
Whatever happened to just singing for no reason? Huh?
아마도 사람들은 이상하게
생각해서 안하는 거겠죠
Maybe people... found it weird....
So, why do you want to leave Ralph Lauren?
왜 랄프 로렌을 그만 두고 싶어하나요?
-What? I-I don't
-You don't?
네? 아닌데요?
아니예요?
저는 거기서 일하는 거 좋아하는데요
No, I-I-I love it there
Well, if you don't want to leave,
why are we having this lunch?
랄프 로렌을 그만두고 싶지 않은데
우리가 왜 점심을 같이 먹고 있는거죠?
(저 사람이 제 상사예요!)
-"That is my boss"
-What?
네?
(저 사람이 제 상사라구요!)
-"That's my boss".
-That's Hugo Boss?
저 사람이 휴고 보스라구요?
여긴 정말 칙칙하네
This place is so depressing.
If I had to work here I'd kill myself
여기서 일하다가는 자살하겠네
확실히 아직 (자살) 안하셨네요~
But you obviously haven't
무엇을 도와드릴까요?
How can I help you?
성을 좀 바꾸려구요
I need to change my name, please. See, I need to change it because I'm-I'm hiding from the law
제가 법을 좀 피해 있어야 해서요
재미있는 분이시군요
You're fun
이 양식을 다 채워주셔야 합니다
You need to fill out this form
근데 어떻게 해야할지 잘 모르겠는데요
Okay, well, I just don't, I don't know how it works exactly
See, my name is Buffay and my husband's name is Hannigan,
제 성은 부페이고
제 남편 성은 해니건인데
so is it supposed to be Buffay-Hannigan or Hannigan-Buffay?
부페이-해니건으로 해야 하나요?
아님 해니건-부페이로 해야 하나요?
아무거나 원하시는대로 하시면 됩니다
It can be anything you want
아무 거나요?
-Well, not anything, I mean...
-Yeah... anything
네, 아무 거나요
시간이 좀 걸리겠는데요?
Oh, this could take a while
- 줄에서 좀 비켜주시죠
- 네
-Get out of my line
-Okay
안녕~
- Hey!
- Hey Pheebs.
안녕, 피비~
이제 아니야, 오늘 바꿨어
Oh, not anymore. I changed it today
미안해, 해니건 부인
Oh, I'm sorry, mrs Hannigan
또 틀렸지롱~
Wrong again!
사실 마음대로 바꿀 수 있다고 그래서
Apparently you can change it to anything you want
나는 내 이름이 창조적으로
될 수 있는 기회라고 생각한거야
So I thought, all right, here's an opportunity to be creative
그래서 콘수엘라 바나나 해먹
공주로 바꿨어!
So meet Princess Consuela Banana Hammock
그걸로 우리 아기 이름
지으려고 했는데
That's what we were gonna name the baby
피비
- Phoebe!
- Uh! Princess Consuela.
아니지, 콘수엘라 공주야
너 진짜로 이름 그렇게 바꾼거야?
- You seriously changed your name to that?
- Uh-huh!
응
그럼 이제부터 우리는 널
콘수엘라 공주라고 불러야 되는거야?
Okay, so from now on we have to call you Princess Consuela?
아니, 내 친구들은 나를
발레리라고 부르게 할 거야
Uhm, no. I'm gonna have my friends call me Valerie
안녕, 면접은 어떻게 됐어?
Hey, how'd the interview go?
Oh! It's not good.
별로였어
그거 알아? 난 언제나
면접 후에는 그렇게 느끼는데
You know, I always feel that way after an interview
I'll bet it went better than you think.
난 네가 생각하는 거보다
훨씬 더 나을 거라고 장담해
Well, I didn't get the job at Gucci
and I got fired from Ralph Lauren
글쎄, 난 구찌에 취직 못했고
랄프 로렌에서 짤렸어
그거 참 안좋은 면접이네
That is a bad interview
그게 무슨 소리야?
어떻게 그렇게 된거야?
What are you, what are you talking about?
How did this happen?
내 상사가 내가 면접보던
레스토랑에 있었던 거야
Well, my boss was at the same restaurant where I was having my interview and he heard everything
그리고는 면접 내용을 다 들었어
그리고는 나중에 상사가 나한테
전화를 해서 나를 놔주겠다는거야
So later he calls me to his office and he tells me that he's gonna have to let me go,
내가 팀원이 아니라면서
because I'm not a team player.
And I said "Wait a minute! Yes I am."
그래서 "아녜요! 저 팀원 맞아요" 했어
그랬더니...
and I had to sit there for 45 minutes while he proved that that in fact... was true.
그 사람이 내가 팀원이
아니라고 밝혀내는
45분 내내 앉아있어야 했어
Oh God. I'm so sorry
어떡하니... 안됐다
안녕~ 이게 뭐지??
Hey! Wha-hoo! What's this?
Well it's a, it's a bottle of champagne. Why is this here?
샴페인이잖아!!
왜 이게 여기 있는거지?
로스
-Ross...
-I guess it's here because I GOT TENURE!
내가 종신 재임 교수가
되었기 때문이지!!
와~ 축하해
Congratulations!
오늘은 나의 교수 경력에 있어서
굉장한 날이야
This is the single greatest day of my professional career.
Gunther, six glasses!
건터, 잔 6개 주세요
6개요? 내가 동참했음 좋겠어요?
Six? You want me to join you?
전 조이가 여기 있는 줄 알았어요
5개가 좋겠네요
Oh, I thought Joey was here. Five is good
내일은 구린 커피를 먹겠는데?
Well, I'm gonna have a loogie in my coffee tomorrow
Ooh! Israeli champagne. And it's vanilla!
이스라엘 샴페인이네~
바닐라 맛인데?
난 종신 재임 교수가 된 거지
복권 당첨된게 아니야
I got tenure. I didn't win the lottery...
Hey Rach, so uh... how did your thing go?
레이첼~ 어떻게 됐어?
Oh it... good! Yeah, but I'm not gonna hear
from that for a couple of days
잘됐어... 근데 며칠 뒤에
결과를 듣게 될 것 같아
그거 알아? 넌 꼭 될 거야
난 느껴진다니까
Oh, you know what? You're gonna get it
I-I-I-I can feel it.
느껴지니?
- Can you?
- Ah, all right. Here's to Ross!
로스를 위하여~
And-and to years of hard work finally paying off
그리고 드디어 2년 동안 열심히
일한 대가를 받는 사람을 위해~
그리고 말하자면 직업은
그렇게 중요한 게 아니야~
And to knowing that your career doesn't mean everything
하지만 말하자면 그건 아주 중요해~
But also knowing it means a lot
더 중요한 건 균형적으로 살아가는 거야
But more importantly to full well-rounded lives
그게 직업 중심으로 사는 거지
...that center around work
로스를 위하여~
- To Ross!
- Ross!
이게 가장 최고인 부분이 뭔지 알아?
You know what the best part about this is?
I can never be fired
난 절대로 해고 당하지 않는다는 거야!
이런...
No seriously. I have job security for life
난 평생동안 직업을 보장받을 거라구
알아? 난 절대로 걱정하지 않아도 돼~
You know, I never have to worry
Oh, look at you. Look how happy you are for me
봐봐~ 나 때문에 얼마나 행복해 하는지
아니야, 그게 아니야
No, it's not that. I got fired today
And I didn't get the other job
나 오늘 해고 당했어
그리고 구찌도 안됐어
레이첼, 미안해
Rach, I'm so sorry
Great. I feel like an idiot
난 진짜 바보같아
아니야, 괜찮아, 넌 몰랐잖아
No, it's okay, you didn't know
Oh...Little heads-up would have been nice
귓뜸 좀 해주지 그랬어
다시 집을 보여주셔서 감사해요
Thank you for letting us see the house again
그리고 그 조건부 날인 증서에
다시 한번 설명해주셔서 감사해요
And thank you for explaining to us what escrow means...
벌써 다 까먹었지만 어쨌든 고마워요
I've already forgotten what you said, but thank you
있고 싶은 만큼 있으세요
Take as long as you want
Just let me know when you're through
다 보시고 나면 말씀해주세요
Ah, so glad you decided to come
네가 와보기로 결정한 거 정말 기뻐
나도야, 여기 되게 좋네
Me too. Yeah, this place is great
I'm so happy for you guys. Although, you know
I hope you like fungus
정말 기뻐!
너희가 곰팡이를 좋아하는 걸
바래야 하지만
뭐라구?
- What?
- Fungus! Yeah. Place is full of it
곰팡이! 아주 꽉 차있네~
아니야, 그렇지 않아
No it's not. We had an inspection
and they didn't find anything
우리가 정밀하게 검사를 했는데
아무 것도 안나왔어
알았어
Okay. Then I guess I have dry eyes
and a scratchy throat for no reason
그럼 내 눈이 건조해지고
목이 따가운 건 대체 뭐 때문일까?
아마도 네가 여기 올 때
차 안에서 내내 개처럼
Maybe because it's you hung your head out of the window
like a dog the whole ride here.
머리를 창 밖에 내놔서 그런 거겠지
Maybe. So this is the living room huh? Ooh, it's pretty dark
그래, 그건 그렇다 치자
그래, 여기가 거실이야?
진짜 어둡네~
아니야, 어둡지 않아
No it's not!
장난해? 난 구석에 박쥐가
있는 걸 본 것 같은데
Are you kiddin'?
I think I just saw a bat in the corner!
너 머리를 창 밖에 내놨을 때
When your head was hanging out the window,
it didn't hit a mailbox, did it?
우체통에 머리 박았지, 그렇지?
아마도
Maybe. Well, I just think you guys can do better than this house, you know?
난 그냥 너희가 이 집보다
더 좋은 집에서 살 수 있다고 봐
Or any other house for that matter.
다른 어떤 집들도 마찬가지고
Oh Joey, look, we know you're having a hard time with this, but we really, we love it here
조이
우리도 네가 받아들이기
힘들다는 걸 알지만 여길 좋아해
여기가 좋아
FINE, ok, if you love this house so much, then you should just live here, okay?
알았어, 그렇게 이 집이 좋으면
그냥 여기 살아
알았지? 난 그냥 너희가 이 이상한
허밍소리에 익숙해지길 바란다
I just hope you get used to that weird humming sound
조이, 그거 네가 내는 소리란 거 다 알아
Joey, we know that's you
아니야, 나 아니야
no... hmmmmm... it's not... hmmmmmmmmmm
안녕~ 잘 왔어
- Hey!Welcome back!
- Ah! I missed you
보고 싶었어
- Oh, me too!
- So, what's new?
나도
새로운 게 뭐지?
Well, I'm no longer Phoebe Buffay
글쎄, 난 이제 더이상
피비 부페이가 아니야
That's great! You changed you name?
대단하다~ 너 이름 바꾼거야?
응, 바꿨어~
Yes I did! Meet: Princess Consuela Banana Hammock!
콘수엘라 바나나 해먹 공주를
소개합니다!
장난치는 거지?
- You're kidding right?
- Nope
아니
- You really did that?
- Yep
- 너 정말 그렇게 바꿨어?
- 응!
그렇게 하면 안되잖아
Yeah, but you can't do that
왜?
Why? It's fun, it's different, no-one else has a name like it
재미있고, 색다르고
다른 어떤 사람도 그런 이름 없잖아
좋았어, 나도 이름 바꿔야지
Alright, then I'm gonna change my name
좋아~ 자기는 뭘로 바꿀건데?
Great, okay, what are you gonna change it to?
크랩 백(쓰레기 봉다리)
Crap Bag!
마이크 크랩 백?
Mike Crap Bag?
아니, 마이크 말고
No, no Mike, just Crap Bag. First name Crap, last name Bag
그냥 크랩 백
이름은 크랩(쓰레기) 성은 백(봉다리)
진담 아니지?
You're not serious, right?
아니야, 진담이야
Yeah, I'm serious. It's fun, it's different and no-one else has a name like that!
재미있고, 색다르고
다른 어떤 사람도 그런 이름 없잖아
Uhu, uhu, well, then, great. If you love it, I love it
그럼 좋네~
네가 그 이름이 좋으면 나도 좋아
난 정말 그 이름 좋아
I do love it, and I love your name. I love Princess Consuela
난 자기 이름도 정말 좋아
콘수엘라 공주
난 크랩이 좋아
And I love Crap
Ow!
누구세요?
Who are you?
Oh, hi, I'm Joey. My stupid friends are buying this house. Who are you?
안녕! 난 조이야
내 바보같은 친구들이
이 집 산대, 넌 누구니?
I'm Mackenzie. My stupid parents are selling this house
전 맥켄지예요
제 바보같은 부모님들이 이 집 판대요
전 부모님이 싫어요
I hate my parents
나도 내 친구들이 싫어
I hate my friends
Alright, look. There's gotta be a way that we can stop this from happening
내 친구들이 이 집을 사지 못하게 할
좋은 방법이 있을 거야
어떤 방법이요?
Like what?
Uhm... oh! Okay. You come with me, and you tell them that the house is haunted!
나랑 같이 가서 내 친구들한테
이 집에 귀신이 붙었다고 그러자
딱 여덟살 수준이잖아요?
What are you? Eight?
Woah, uh! Okay, let's hear your great idea
알았어, 그럼 네 뛰어난
방법이나 얘기해봐
전 뛰어난 방법이 없는데요
I don't have any great ideas. I am eight.
전 여덟살이거든요
Ahh! There's gotta be a way. I mean, you know,
방법이 있을 거야
모니카랑 챈들러가 여기로 이사오면
if Monica and Chandler move out here and now Phoebe is married to Mike
이제 피비는 마이크랑 결혼했고
그럼 단지 레이첼이랑 로스랑
나 뿐이라는 얘기야
That just leaves me and Ross and Rach, you know what I mean?
무슨 뜻인지 알겠지?
아니요
I really don't
What am I gonna do, I feel like I'm losing my friends
난 지금 내 친구들을
잃고 있는 것 같단 말이야
제 부모님들은 저보고
새 친구들을 만들래요
My parents say I'm gonna make new friends
너한테는 쉽겠지
넌 어리고, 난 그냥 내 나이잖아
Oh, yeah, sure, easy for you, you're young. Me, I'm set in my ways
This is what my mom was talking about
우리 엄마가 그러는데요
이래서 징징대는 사람은
소심하다고 했어요
Whiners are wieners
Look, you want your friends to be happy, right?
봐요, 친구들이 행복해지는 걸 원하죠?
Yeah, yeah, I guess
그럼, 그렇게 생각해
여기로 이사오는게 친구들이
행복해 지는 거라면
Well, if moving here is gonna make them happy, don't you want them to do it?
못오게 할 건가요?
아니, 아마도 오게 해야겠지
Yeah, maybe
그럼 그렇게 해줘요
Then you gotta let them go
인정하긴 싫지만
I hate to admit it, but you're probably right. How did you get to be so smart?
네 말이 맞아
너 어떻게 그렇게 똑똑하게 됐니?
책을 많이 읽어요
I read a lot
난 우리가 친구가 될 수 있다고 생각했어
Just when I thought we could be friends
안녕하세요, 레이첼?
금방 들었어요, 안됐네요
Hey Rach, I just heard. I'm so sorry
고마워요
Oh, thank you...
아직까지 제 이름 모르죠? 그쵸?
You still don't know my name, do you?
이젠 그럴 필요가 없잖아요?
Well, now I don't have to
로스, 왜 그렇게 오래 걸려?
Ross, what is taking you so long?
미안해
I'm sorry, it's almost as if this wasn't built for a quick getaway!
빠른 출입구를 안만들어서 그런거야
레이첼?
- Rachel?
- Mark? Oh my God!
마크? 세상에~
어떻게 지냈어?
- How've you been?
- I'm fantastic. You remember Ross?
정말 반갑네
로스 생각나지?
그럼
Sure, sure. What's with the chair
의자 가지고 뭐해요?
Uh, you know, you can't always get a seat on the subway, so...
언제나 지하철에서 앉을 수
있잖아요, 그래서...
현명하네~
Clever. So how are you?
어떻게 지내?
썩 잘 지내고 있지는 못하지
Oh, well, you're not catching me on my best day
Yeah, a box full of your desk stuff doesn't exactly say big promotion
네 물건 잔뜩 가지고 나가는 게
승진한 거 같아 보이진 않는다
하지만 좋아
좀 쉬면서 자선활동도 하고...
No, but it's good, you know, I'm gonna take some time off and do some charity work
진짜야?
Are you sure, because we may have something at Louis Vuitton
하지만 어쩌면 루이 비통에서도
일이 좀 있을 것 같은데?
그거 참 좋은 자선활동이지, 뭔데?
Well, screw charity work. What've you got?
오늘 저녁 먹으면서 얘기하는게 어때?
Why don't we have dinner tonight and talk about it?
Great! I'll call ya!
- 좋아
- 좋아~
- 전화할게
- 그래
만나서 반가웠어요
Nice to see you
그래, 난 종신재임교수 됐어요
Yeah! yeah, I got tenure!
Oh my God!
오 세상에~
봤지? 내가 좋은 일이
생길 거라 얘기 했잖아
See? I told you something good would come along
And he seemed really nice. I've met him before?
그리고 아까 걔 되게 괜찮아 보이더라
전에 내가 만난 적이 있던가?
Ross! That's Mark. From Bloomingdales? You were insanely jealous of him
로스, 마크야
블루밍데일에서 너 미친듯이
질투했었잖아
저 사람이 마크라고?
That is Mark?
I hate that guy
그래
나 저 놈 정말 싫어
안돼, 너 오늘 쟤랑 저녁 먹지 마
No, no, NO, you cannot go to dinner with him
너 내가 일하는 걸 원하지 않는거야?
What? You don't want me to get a job?
확실히 저 놈이 너한테 일을 줄 거야
Oh yeah, I'm sure he's gonna give you a job. Maybe make you his SEXretary
아마도 자기 섹스 비서겠지
난 진심이야
진짜로 난 저 자식 못믿겠어
I'm serious. I just don't trust that guy, okay?
로스, 그거 알아?
Ross, you know what?
나중에 얘기 하자
경비 아저씨들 온다
Okay, let's talk about it later, there comes security
난 이 길이 너무 마음에 들어
Oh, I love this street. The trees, the big front yards, the actual picket fences
나무들이랑, 큰 앞마당이랑
진짜 울타리랑
이런, 저 개 두마리가
그거 하려고 그러네
Man, those two dogs are going at it!
- 안녕
- 안녕, 어디 갔었어?
- Hey!
- Hey, where have you been?
그냥 여기 저기 둘러봤어
Oh, just er... you know, looking around.
But you know what? This house... is great.
그거 알아? 이 집은 정말 좋아
정말이야?
왜 마음이 바뀐거야?
Really? What changed your mind?
Oh well, the little girl who lives here made me feel a lot better about the whole thing
여기 사는 꼬마 여자애를 만났는데
그 애가 모든 걸 더
잘 받아들이게 해주더라고
조이, 여기 사는 꼬마 여자 애가 있었지
Joey, there was a little girl who lived here, but she died like 30 years ago
근데 그 애는 30년 전에 죽었어
- What?
- Ha! I'm just messing with you.
뭐라고?
그냥 너 놀리려고 그런 거야
하나도 안재미있어
That's not funny! You know I'm afraid of little girl ghosts!
넌 내가 꼬마 여자 귀신을
얼마나 무서워하는 걸 알잖아
조이, 이제 이 집이 괜찮으면
네 방 가볼래?
Joey, now that you're okay with the house, do you wanna go see your room
뭐라고? 내 방이 있다고?
What? I get my own room?
우리가 조이방도 없는
집을 살 거라고 생각했냐?
You don't think we'd buy a house and not have a Joey room do you?
오 맙소사!!
Oh my God! Oh! Hey, can I have an aquarium? And a sex swing?
나 수족관이랑 섹스 스윙 설치해도 돼?
아니
No!
왜? 물통 청소 깨끗하게 할게
Why not? I'll keep the tank clean
바나나 해먹 양이 먼저 가시죠
After you, miss Banana Hammock
Thank you, mister Bag.
고마워요, 백씨
- 안녕~
- 안녕하세요
Oh hey, how are you?
- 어떻게 지내?
- 잘 지내요
Oh hi Rita! Good! Oh, Rita's a massage client
리다는 마사지 손님이야
Oh! Why don't you introduce me?
그래? 왜 날 소개시켜주지 않는거지?
리다, 이 사람이 제 남편이예요
Er, Rita, this is my husband
- Oh!
- Yeah.
자기, 왜 내 이름 왜 얘기 안해?
Why don't you tell her my name?
알았어, 할 거야
Okay, I will. This is my husband Crap Bag
이 사람은 제 남편 크랩 백이예요
크랩 백?
Crap Bag?
쉽게 외우려면 그냥
쓰레기 봉다리를 생각하세요
If you need an easy way to remember it, just think of a bag of crap.
알았어요, 실례할게요
Okay. Excuse me...
Ogh... Okay, fine. You made your point. Can you please just be Mike Hannigan again?
알았어, 좋아, 자기가 이겼어
그냥 마이크 해니건으로
다시 돌아와줄래?
자기가 피비 부페이로
다시 돌아온다면
Only if you'll be Phoebe Buffay
부페이-해니건은 어때?
How about uhm... How about Buffay-Hannigan?
정말?
Really?
Yeah. I'm Phoebe Buffay-Hannigan Banana Hammock
나는 피비 부페이-해니건
바나나 해먹이야
자기, 바나나 해먹이
무슨 뜻인 줄이나 아는 거야?
Do you even know what a banana hammock is?
그냥 재미있는 말이잖아
It's a funny word
그건 * 스피도 란 말야
* 남자용 삼각 수영 팬티
It's a Speedo
Oh crap!
젠장
여기 레이첼 있어?
Hey, is Rachel here?
No
아니
아직 저녁먹으러 가서 안온거야?
She's still at dinner?
그런 것 같아, 누구랑 갔는데?
I guess. Why? Who's she with?
블루밍데일에서 같이 일했던
마크라는 자식
That guy Mark. From Bloomingdale's...
레이첼은 그냥 그 놈이
잘해주는 거라고 생각해
She thinks he's just being nice to her. But I know he really wants to sleep with her
하지만 나는 그 놈이 레이첼하고
자고 싶어하는 걸 알지
It's seven years ago. My time machine works!
7년 전 일이잖아
내 타임머신이 작동한다~
레이첼이랑 내가 길에서
그 놈이랑 우연히 마주쳤거든
We ran into him on the street today and he said he might have a job for her
그 놈은 "일자리를 소개시켜
줄 지도 모른다"고 말했지만
그냥 그 놈은 레이첼이랑
자고 싶은 거라고
But I know he just wants to get into her pants
왜 둘이 자면 안되는데?
So what if he wants to sleep with her? I mean, she's single and he's cute
레이첼은 싱글이고
마크는 멋있잖아
뭐라고?
Excuse me?
자기... 어제 지하철에서
왕가슴 계속 쳐다봤잖아
Oh please! Yesterday on the subway?
You couldn't stop staring at that woman with the big breasts the whole time.
참고로 말하자면
For your information, I was staring at her baby. We're about to be parents
난 그 여자의 아기를 계속 쳐다본거야
우린 이제 부모가 될 거잖아
Oh, sorry!
미안해
안녕, 얘들아~
- Hi you guys!
- Hey, so uhm... How was dinner?
그래~ 저녁은 어땠어?
Oh, it was great. Mark is so sweet.
너무 좋았어, 마크는 너무 친절해
그래?
Oh yeah? Yeah? I wonder why?
What could that smarmy letch possibly want?
난 왜 그렇게 친절한지 궁금하네
뭘 원하는 건 아닐까?
Oh Ross, come on. He's happily married
His wife just had twins
로스, 제발... 마크는 행복하게
결혼생활을 하고 있고
부인이 얼마 전에 쌍둥이를 낳았대
아기들을 위해서 뭐라도
보내야하지 않을까?
Should we send something?
일은 어떻게 됐는데?
How did the job stuff go?
He offered me one
마크가 일을 제안했어
잘 됐다~!
- That's great!
- Congratulations!
축하해~
그래, 끝내주지??
I know, it's amazing. It's amazing.
랄프 로렌에서 했던 일하고는
비교도 안될만큼 끝내주는 일이야
It's so much better than what I had at Ralph Lauren. The money is great...
특히 급여조건이 아주 훌륭하지
잠깐만
Can we, can we just stop for a second?
누가 더 좋은 일이 생길 거라고
얘기 했지?
Who said something better would come along, huh? You didn't believe me
넌 안믿었지만 내가 모두
잘 될 거라고 말했잖아
I told you everything was gonna work out.
You know what? This calls for a bottle of Israels finest.
이건 '이스라엘 파이니스트(술 이름)'
한병 감이라고
근데 일이 파리에서 하는거야
The job is in Paris
내 말은 드라마는
진짜 인기가 있긴 한데
I mean, this soap opera is a great gig, but... am I missing opportunities?
내가 지금 기회를 놓치는 거야?
나는 내가 심각한 배우라고
생각해왔단 말이야
You know, I've always thought of myself as a serious actor
내가 독립 영화에 더 출연해야 되니?
I mean, should I be trying to do more independent movies?
모르겠는데요
I don't know... You know what?
있잖아요? 제 곰인형 바꿔드릴게요
I'm gonna put you on with my bear. Hold on.
잠깐만요
안녕, 곰! 난 지금
중대한 충고가 필요해
Hey bear, I need some career advice